Mss.B.J44 Mss.B.J44
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 8, 1922; 11x8-1/2; Shull, A. Franklin (Aaron Franklin), b. 1881
    Ann Arbor, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a lecture to be given of evolution or genetics.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 11, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Shull, A. Franklin (Aaron Franklin), b. 1881
    Ann Arbor, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning lectures he is to give.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 17, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Shull, A. Franklin (Aaron Franklin), b. 1881
    Ann Arbor, Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning lectures.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 24, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Shull, A. Franklin (Aaron Franklin), b. 1881
    Ann Arbor, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his lectures.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 17, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Shull, A. Franklin (Aaron Franklin), b. 1881
    Ann Arbor, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Sorry he is ill and cannot lecture.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, March 3, 1923; 11x8-1/2; Shull, A. Franklin (Aaron Franklin), b. 1881
    Ann Arbor, Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning some lectures he is to give.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 18, 1930; Shute, D. Kerfoot (Daniel Kerfoot), 1858-1935
    Washington, Typed L.S. 3p.and enc.of 1p. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter on his book on genetics
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 8, 1930; 8-1/2x5-1/2; Shute, D. Kerfoot (Daniel Kerfoot), 1858-1935
    Washington, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Certificate of membership issued to Herbert S. Jennings, March 24, 1905; 16-1/2 x 21; Sigma Xi
    D.S.: John Marshall, president and Owen Louis Shinn, secretary. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, April 20, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Smith, J Whitefield
    Bloomington, I11., Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Dec. 28, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Sonneborn, T. M. (Tracy Morton), 1905-1981
    A.L.S. 1p. In pencil. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards his paper and slides.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Jan. 13, 1942; 11x8-1/2; Spencer, R. R. (Roscoe Roy), 1888-1982
    Los Angeles, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for reprints.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings. Berkeley, July 16, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Spencer, Steven M
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning abstracts of his lectures at the U of P bicentennial celebration.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 23, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Stout, Arlow Burdette, 1876-1957
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p.and end. (see H.S: Jennings papers.) Concerning paramecium.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Los Angeles, June 26, 1941; 10-1/2x7-1/2; Swain, Robert E. (Robert Eckles), b. 1875
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Los Angeles, June 28, 1941; 10-1/2x7-1/2; Swain, Robert E. (Robert Eckles), b. 1875
    Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, New York, April 14, 1931; 10-1/2x7-1/4; Sweet, Norman
    Fort Wayne, Ind., Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter. Forwards brochure on his new book.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, June 16, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Taylor, Charles Vincent, 1885-1946
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, July 21, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Taylor, Charles Vincent, 1885-1946
    Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the meeting of the AAAS.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, July 26, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Taylor, Charles Vincent, 1885-1946
    Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Will publish his article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, July 31, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Taylor, Charles Vincent, 1885-1946
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Los Angeles, June 30, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Thayer, John B. (John Borland), b. 1894
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the U of P bicentennial celebration.
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Los Angeles, July 24, 1939; 11x8-1/2; Thayer, John B. (John Borland), b. 1894
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Los Angeles, March 7, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Thayer, John B. (John Borland), b. 1894
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, March 19, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Thayer, John B. (John Borland), b. 1894
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Los Angeles, June 7, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Thayer, John B. (John Borland), b. 1894
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, June 14, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Thayer, John B. (John Borland), b. 1894
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the publication of his talk at the U of P bicentennial celebration.
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Los Angeles, June 19, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Thayer, John B. (John Borland), b. 1894
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the bicentennial celebration of the U of P.
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Los Angeles, June 25, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Thayer, John B. (John Borland), b. 1894
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his stay at the U of P bicêntennial celebration.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Los Angeles, July 15, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Thayer, John B. (John Borland), b. 1894
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his lectures for the U of P bicentennial celebration.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Oct. 10, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Thayer, John B. (John Borland), b. 1894
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his lecture at the U of P bicentennial celebration.
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Los Angeles, Oct. 14, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Thayer, John B. (John Borland), b. 1894
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) ----Copy. Concerning publication of his articles delivered at the U of P bicentennial celebration.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Oct. 24, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Thayer, John B. (John Borland), b. 1894
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards expenses for his trip to the U of P bicentennial celebration.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Berkeley, Dec. 8, 1943; 11x8-1/2; The Abraham Lincoln School, Chicago
    Chicago, Typed L.S.: Karl H. Niebyl. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks him to write a monograph for publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, April 26, 1920; 11x8-1/2; The American year book
    New York, Typed L.S.: F.G.Wickware. 1P.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Aug. 30, 1930; The general press cutting association,ltd.
    London, Typed L.S.with initials: W.H[arvey]. 1p.and enc.of 1p. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Would be glad to send him clippings for a fee.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Aug. 16, 1946; 11x8-1/2; The Nation Associates
    Hollywood, Calif., Typed L.S.: Bartley C.Crum and Bette Davis. 1p. (see H.S.Jennings papers.) Concerning a liberal movement in politics.
  - Letter to H.S. Jennings, Los Angeles, March 30, 1945; 11x8-1/2; The Nation associates
    Typed L.S.: Freda Kirchwey. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning the aim of the Associates.
  - Letter to H.S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Oct. 16, 1944; 11x8-1/2; The Nation associates
    New York, Typed L.S.: Freda Kirchwey. 2p.and enc. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks him to join their organization.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, April 21, 1931; 10x7-1/2; The New republic
    New York, Typed L.S.: Mary E. Updike. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a book review.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, April 15, 1931; 10x7-1/2, 13x8-1/2; The Parents' magazine
    New York, Typed L.S.: Mary E. Buchanan. 1p. and enc.of 5p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards radio program in which one of his books is highly recommended (on genetics.)
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb.14, 1931; 10x7, 10-1/2x8-1/2; The Parents' magazine
    New York, Typed L.S.: George J. Hecht. 1p.and enc.of 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) His work is commended by the magazine.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, July 30, 1920; 5-1/2x8-1/2; The philosophical review
    Ithaca, N.Y., Typed L.S.: J.E. Creighton. 2p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers) Asks him to review a book.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Sept. 22, 1920; 3-1/4x5-1/2; The philosophical review
    Ithaca, N.Y., Printed postal card, filled in in ms. 1p.and add. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a book review.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Sept. 13, 1921; 11x8-1/2; The Philosophical Review
    Ithaca, N.Y., Typed L.S.: J.E. Creighton. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a book review.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, May 3, 1920; 11x8-1/2 and 5-1/2x3-1/2; The Science press
    Garrison, N.Y., Typed L.S. 1p.and enc.of 1p., end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, March 26, 1924; 11x8-1/2; The science press
    Lancaster, Typed L.S.: A.E.Urban. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, May 2, 1945; 11x8-1/2; The Science press
    New York, Typed L.S.: Jaques Cattell. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for book review.
  - Telegram to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Dec. 5, 1922; 6-3/4x8-1/2; The Science Service
    D. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Wishes summary of his address on Mendel and evolution.
  - Letter to W[herbert] S. Jennings, June 12, 1923; 11x 8-1/2; The Survey
    New York, Typed L.S.: Bruno Lasker. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Wishes he would write a report on immigration.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Woods Hole, Mass., June 21, 1923; 8-1/2x5-1/2; The Survey
    New York, Typed L.S.: Bruno Lasker. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning immigration.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 25, 1923; 11x8-1/2; The Survey
    New York, Typed L.S.: Geddes Smith. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business of his article on immigration.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Oct. 31, 1923; 8-1/2x5-1/2; The Survey
    New York, Typed L.S.: Geddes Smith. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 8, 1923; 8-1/2x5-1/2; The Survey
    New York, Typed L.S.: Geddes Smith. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 23, 1923; 8-1/2x5-1/2; The Survey
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Nov. 26, 1923; 11x8-1/2; The Survey
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 1, 1923; 11x8-1/2; The Survey
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 8, 1923; 8-1/2x5-1/2; The Survey
    New York, Typed L.S.: Mary W. Herring. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers) Business.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 26, 1923; 11x8-1/2; The Survey
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, May, 1945; 5-1/2x8-1/2; The Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology
    Philadelphia, Typed L. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning an article which will be published.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Los Angeles, June 1, 1945; 3-1/4x5-1/2; The Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology
    Philadelphia, Typed L.on postal card. 1p.and add. (see H.S. Jennings papers) Concerning an article of his.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, July 10, 1945; 3-1/4x5-1/2; The Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology
    Philadelphia, Typed L.on postal card. 1p.and add. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards reprints.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Philadelphia, Oct. 16, 1920; 10x8; Tillinghast, Frank N
    Greenport, N.Y., A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks information concerning his latest publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, April 30, 1921; 11x8-1/2; Titus, Charles P
    New York, A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S.Jennings papers.) Asks for publication on rotifera.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Los Angeles, Feb. 26, 1945; 11x8-1/2; United States. Navy
    Los Angeles, Typed L.S.: O.M. Murphy. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for information on his foreign residence.
  - Diploma to Herbert S. Jennings, June 29, 1893; 18-1/2x23-1/2; University of Michigan
    Printed D.S.: James B. Angell, pres.and James H. Wade, sec. 1p. Parchment. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Diploma to Herbert Spencer Jennings, June 7, 1918; 19x25; University of Michigan
    D.S.: Harry B. Hutchins, pres.and Shirley W. Smith, sec. 1p. In Latin. Parchment. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Diploma to Herbert Spencer Jennings, May 18, 1938; 18-1/2x23-1/2; University of Pennsylvania
    D.S.: Thomas S. Gates, pres., and Edward W. Mumford, sec. 1p. In Latin. Parchment. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Diploma to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Sept. 21, 1940; 19x23-1/2; University of Pennsylvania
    D.S.: Thomas S. Gates, pres.and Edward W. Mumford, sec. 1p. Parchment. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Los Angeles, April 19, 1941; 8-1/2x5-1/2; University of Pennsylvania. Press
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S.: Phelps Soule. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards galley proofs of an article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 15, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Van der Lyn, Theodore N
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Would like a reprint of an article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Oct. 8, [1941]; 3-1/4x5-1/2; Vaughan, B C jr
    Kansas City, A.L.S.on postal card. 1p.,end.and add. (see H.S. Jennings papers) Asks for reprint.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Sept. 12, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Vaughan, Thomas Wayland, 1870-1952
    Washington, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning variation of the foraminifera.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Sept. 27, 1941; 8x5; Vaughan, Thomas Wayland, 1870-1952
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, April 13, 1934; 11x8-1/2; Visscher, J Paul
    Cleveland O., Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for reprints.
  - Account with H[erbert] S. Jennings, Jan. 27, July 25, 1933, 1942; W.W. Norton & Company
    D. 4p. Various sizes. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Account with H[erbert] S. Jennings, Jan. 25, Jan. 27, 1939, 1941; 11x8-1/2; W.W. Norton & Company
    Printed D.filled in in ms.S.: H.P.Wilson. 4p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, April 5, 1933; 8-1/2x5-1/2; W.W. Norton & Company
    New York, Typed L. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a letter from Germany pertaining to a German edition of his work.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, June 4, 1945; 11x8-1/2; W.W. Norton & Company
    New York, Typed L.S.: H. P. Wilson. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning royalty difficulties.
  - Letter to F.V.Morley, London, March 10, 1931; 11x8-1/2; W.W. Norton & Company
    New York, Typed L. 1p. Copy. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a request by H.S.Jennings.
  - Statement of royalties to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Jan. 25, Jan. 27, 1939, 1941; 11x8-1/2; W.W. Norton & Company
    Printed D.filled in in type. 4p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.)
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Aug. 27, 1921; 6x9; Wagner Free Institute of Science
    Philadelphia, A.L.S. John G. Rothermel. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, March 31, 1924; 6x9; Wagner Free Institute of Science
    Philadelphia, A.L.S.: John G. Rothermel. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Business.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Baltimore, July 12, 1919; 11x8-1/2; Walcutt, Charles C
    Washington, Typed L.S. 1p.,end.with telegram from Jennings to Walcutt. Enc.of wire from Jennings to Cowles. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning R. P. Cowles.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, July 14, 1919; 11x8-1/2; Walcutt, Charles C
    Washington, Typed L.S. 1p.and end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a cable to R.P.Cowles.
  - Telegram to [Herbert S. Jennings], July 16, [1919]; 6-3/4x8-1/2; Walcutt, Charles C
    Telegram. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning R.P. Cowles.
  - Note to [Herbert S.] Jennings, [Jan.?, [1924]; 3x5-1/2; Walter, H E
    Providence, R.I.; Printed N. filled in in ms. S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for publications, especially the one on immigration.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Aug. 22, 1930; 11x8-1/2; Ward, C. H. (Charles Henshaw), 1872-1935
    Typed L.S. 2p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning one of the works.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Sept. 9, 1932; 11x8-1/2; Ward, Henry Baldwin, 1865-1945
    Urbana, Ill., Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S.Jennings papers.) Concerning his publication on rotataria.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 24, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Watson, John B. (John Broadus), 1878-1958
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, March 29, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Watson, John B. (John Broadus), 1878-1958
    New York, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a lecture. Refers to Bertrand Russell.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, April 3, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Watson, John B. (John Broadus), 1878-1958
    New York, Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a lecture. His work on instinct.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, April 8, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Watson, John B. (John Broadus), 1878-1958
    New York, Typed L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a lecture.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, April 14, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Watson, John B. (John Broadus), 1878-1958
    Baltimore; Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a lecture.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Sept. 21, 1942; 3-1/4x5-1/2; Waverly Press
    Baltimore, Printed L.filled in in ms.on postal card. 1p.and add., end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards reprints.
  - Receipt to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, March 16, 1939; 5-1/2x8-1/2; Waverly Press
    Baltimore, Printed D.filled in in type. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers)
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 14, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Weatherby, Jesse Howell, 1903-
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Dec. 19, 1938; 11x8-1/2; Weatherby, Jesse Howell, 1903-
    Richmond, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Will furnish equipment for speeches.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Oct. 11, 1941; 3-1/4x5-1/2; Weaver, Nevin
    Typed L.S.on postal card. 1p.and add. (see H.S. Jennings papers) Asks for reprints.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Feb. 2, 1931; 5-1/2x3-1/4; Weill, Blanche C. (Blanche California), b. 1883
    A.L.on postal card. 1p.and add. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks permission to reproduce from one of his publications.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Feb. 11, 1931; 4x5-1/2; Weill, Blanche C. (Blanche California), b. 1883
    A.L.S. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for aid on problem in genetics.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Oct. 16, 1942; 11x8-1/2; Weir, John Robert, 1912-
    Guelph, Canada, Typed L.S. 1p., end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprint.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, Feb. 11, 1927; 9x6; Welch, William Henry, 1850-1934
    Baltimore, A.L.S. 2p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Would like to introduce him to some people.
  - Letter to Herbert Spencer Jennings, Los Angeles, July 12, 1944; 11x8-1/2; Weller, Charles Frederick, b. 1870
    Conway, N.H., A.L.S. 4p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter. Concerning possible world government.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Feb. 26, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Wenrich, David Henry, 1885-1968
    Philadelphia, Typed L. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Friendly letter. Asks him to participate in a meeting.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, March 6, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Wenrich, David Henry, 1885-1968
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a paper he will deliver.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Sept. 30, 1940; 11x8-1/2; Wenrich, David Henry, 1885-1968
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for his participation in the U of P bicentennial celebration.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 28, 1925; 7-1/4x8-1/2; Wheeler, George C. (George Carlos), 1897-1991
    Syracuse, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprint of an article.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, Sept. 26, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Wheeler, William Morton, 1865-1937
    Cambridge, Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Thanks for book.
  - Letter to Herbert C. [Sic] Jennings, Oct. 18, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Wiggam, Albert Edward, 1871-1957
    Kansas City, Mo.; Typed L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprints.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, Aug. 15, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Williams, Elmer F
    Baltimore, Typed L.S. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning a publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Los Angeles, March 17, 1941; 11x8-1/2; Wistar Institute of Anatomy and Biology
    Philadelphia, Typed L.S.: G.L. Lambert. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning G.F.Gause's article.
  - Letter to [Herbert S.] Jennings, March 17, 1924; 11x8-1/2; Wold, Carmin E
    A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks a question.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, April 9, 1925; 5-1/2x8-1/2; Worcester, Dean A. (Dean Amory), 1889-1982
    Columbus, O., A.L.S. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Asks for reprint of publication.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, Jan. 28, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Yale University Press
    New Haven, Typed L.S.: Eugene A. Davidson. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning publication of some of his lectures.
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, May 5, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Yale University Press
    New Haven, Typed L.S.: Eugene A. Davidson. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Suggests title for his new publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, May 27, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Yale University Press
    New Haven, Typed L.S.: Ruth Bernier. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning galley proofs of his publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, May 31, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Yale University Press
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, June 7, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Yale University Press
  - Letter to Herbert S. Jennings, Baltimore, June 14, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Yale University Press
    New Haven, Typed L.S.: Eugene A. Davidson. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his new publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Baltimore, June 23, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Yale University Press
    New Haven, Typed L.S.: R[uth] Bernier. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards galley proofs of his new publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Woods Hole, Mass., June 24, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Yale University Press
    New Haven, Typed L.S.: Ruth Bernier. 1p.,end. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Forwards galley proofs of his new publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Woods Hole, Mass., Sept. 4, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Yale University Press
    New Haven, Typed L.S.: E. Holliday. 1p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning his publication.
  - Letter to H[erbert] S. Jennings, Woods Hole, Mass., Sept. 11, 1933; 11x8-1/2; Yale University Press
    New Haven, Typed L.S.: Norman V. Donaldson. 2p. (see H.S. Jennings papers.) Concerning books sent out for review.